Create a person class that has attributes: first_name, last_name, and account. Make the account private.
Put a comment at the top describing the class with the sentence above.
Create a function to print the data.
Create a function to access the private data member.
Create 2 objects, one for yourself and another for a friend. Call them me and friend.
Print the results of the __doc__ function.
Print each of the objects.
Call the getter for the private data member with both objects.
Challenge:
1. Automatically assign the account numbers for the accounts as 1 and 2 using a class attribute.

Extensions (required):
  
Add a second class, Account, that has attributes of account number and balance.
This class also has functions for withdrawal (as long as it is balance does not go below 0) and deposit.

  
Let us extend the account class that we can compare 2 accounts. They should be compared based on their balance.
Generate 20 random accounts and order them.
◦Note the sort function uses __lt__.

  
Create Checking and Saving account classes. 
The saving account has an interest rate and withdrawal is not possible; only transfer. 
Checking accounts act like account but require $250 to open the account.